Exercise 1.
In this part, we're going to start with
an exercise of short answer questions in section
2.
Remember that in section 2, there is only
one speaker, and it is not a conversation
between two speakers.
Therefore, the answers may appear before you hear
the key words in the questions.
As you already know, the steps for this
question type are Step 1.
Read the requirement to identify the word limit.
In this exercise, you have to write a
maximum of three words and a number.
In Step 2, you have to read the
questions and underline the keywords.
Here are the keywords
that I highlighted.
Step 3.
You are going to predict what type of
information is missing from each blank and predict
distractors through a quick exercise.
Good job!
Next, we will move to Step 4.
Listen and write the answers in the blanks
in the practice section.
Please remember that the information for correct answers
may appear before you hear the keywords in the
questions.
And don't forget to check grammar and
spelling after writing your answers.
See you soon!